https://pbreserve.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentHomeBuyers GuideBest Paintball GunsMilSim Paintball GunsPaintball Sniper RiflesPaintball PistolsPaintball Guns For KidsAutomatic Paintball GunsMechanical Paintball GunsPump Paintball GunsTop Rated Paintball GunsPaintball Gun PackageMag Fed Paintball GunsWoodsball Paintball GunsBest By PricePaintball Guns Under 150 DollarsAccessoriesPaintball MasksPaintball VestsPaintball TanksPaintball HoppersPaintball BarrelsPaintball PodsAll BrandsTippmann Paintball GunsEmpire Paintball GunsDYE Paintball GunsPlanet Eclipse Paintball GunsSpyder Paintball GunsProduct ReviewsTippmann A5Planet Eclipse Etha 2Tippmann GryphonTippmann 98 CustomBrass Eagle Stingray
MenuHomeBuyers GuideBest Paintball GunsMilSim Paintball GunsPaintball Sniper RiflesPaintball PistolsPaintball Guns For KidsAutomatic Paintball GunsMechanical Paintball GunsPump Paintball GunsTop Rated Paintball GunsPaintball Gun PackageMag Fed Paintball GunsWoodsball Paintball GunsBest By PricePaintball Guns Under 150 DollarsAccessoriesPaintball MasksPaintball VestsPaintball TanksPaintball HoppersPaintball BarrelsPaintball PodsAll BrandsTippmann Paintball GunsEmpire Paintball GunsDYE Paintball GunsPlanet Eclipse Paintball GunsSpyder Paintball GunsProduct ReviewsTippmann A5Planet Eclipse Etha 2Tippmann GryphonTippmann 98 CustomBrass Eagle StingrayPrivacy PolicyWho We AreOur website address is: https://pbreserve.com.What Personal Data We Collect and Why We Collect It?CommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded Content From Other WebsitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.How Long We Retain Your Data?If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What Rights You Have Over Your Data?If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where We Send Your Data?Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.AnalyticsOur site uses Google Analytics and Google Analytics Advertising to help analyze and understand how users navigate it. The tools use “cookies” (small text files placed on your computer) to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form (including IP address), which is transmitted to Google.  You can choose to opt out of Google Analytics as a whole here.We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data, and neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user.In layman’s terms, any and all information we personally collect will be used for analytical purposes only, or for contacting giveaway winners.
